Guide to the Boy Scouts of America Collection of ephemeral material, 1838-1993
Department of Special Collections
- Series X: Conferences and Meetings
  - Conferences, Philmont, NM 1956 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Boy Scout Leaders
    - Finance Training
  - Explorer Leaders' Conferences, Philmont, New Mexico 1956 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Region Two - New York. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting 10/17/64
    - Scout Executives Training Conference 8/31-9/4/65
  - Region Six - Georgia. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting 3/29-30/62
    - Explorer Delegate Conference 6/7-9/63
  - 59th Annual Business Meeting. National Council. Boston, MA 5/22/69 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Tri-Council Operations/Commissioner Conference. Dayton, Ohio 6/3/89 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Boy Scout Registration Card for Annual Meeting n.d. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Program n.d. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Series XI: Education/Training Programs and Scouting Associations
  - Scout Exhibition Program 6/3/26 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - First Annual Boy Scouts' "Be Prepared" Pageant. Oak Park, IL 6/19-21/29 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - First Annual Boy Scout Circus. Hohokus, NJ 4/28-29/33 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Radio Addresses Commemorating the 25th Anniversary of the BSA 2/8/35 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Summer Camp documents. Hendrick Hudson Council, New York 1935-1937 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Scouter's Institute Training Schedule 1936 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scout Circus. Yonkers Armory, NY 2/8/36 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Second Annual Boy Scout Circus. State Armory, Oneonta, NY 5/9/36 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scout Circus. Yonkers Armory, NY 2/6/37 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scout Circus. Ohio 2/12/38 (Box 6, Folder 6&7)
  - Raritan Council Events information packet (ca. 1939) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Boy Scout Circus. MacWilliam Stadium, Perth Amboy, NJ 9/18/40 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Region Seven. Explorer Canoe Base 1940-1965 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Panorama and Circus. Cayuga County Council. Auburn, NY 5/26/45 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Winter Camping - A Training Film (ca. 1945) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Use of the Patrol Method Film in Scoutmaster and Commissioner Training (ca. 1946) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Scout Circus. Gilmore Stadium, Los Angeles, CA 5/2-3/47 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 2nd Bi-Annual Panorama and Circus. Cayuga County Council. Auburn, NY 5/24/47 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - The Scout Circus. State Armory, Yonkers, NY 4/2/49 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Gold Rush! 5/9/49 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Scouting Exposition. National Capital Area Council. Washington, D.C. 11/21/50 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - "Training - Before - Commissioning Project": Commissioner Training Plan and Preliminary Orientation (ca. 1951) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fall Round-Up Material 1952 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Fall Round-Up Material 1953 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Fall Roundup Programs and Aids 1954 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - The Relationships Program of the Boy Scouts of America (with Declaration of Interdependence attached) 12/31/53 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - American Camping Association 3/29/39 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - National Conservation Good Turn Program. Mt. Rainier Council 1954 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Paul Bunyan Logging Company Timber Tally (Round-Up) 1954 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Fall Achievement Roundup Program and Aids 1955 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Scouting Exposition. Washington Irving Council. White Plains, NY 4/18/59 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - National Training Events. Philmont Scout Ranch, NM/Schiff Scout Reservation NJ 1961 - 1962 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Scouting Exposition. White Plains, NY 4/15/61 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Scouting in Action Exposition. Teaneck Armory, NJ 4/28-30/61 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Charter Day Kit (ca. 1962) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Exploring Outdoors. High Adventure Superactivities. Great Salt Lake Council, Utah 1963 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Volunteer Training Program. Washington Irving Council 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Scouting Exposition. Washington Irving Council. White Plains, NY. 3/16/63 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - National Junior Leader Instructor Training Camp Staff Guide. Schiff Scout Reservation and Philmont Scout Ranch 3/68 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reunion of the 1st Gilwell Park Group, Sussex, UK 9/6-8/68 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Eagle Scout Recognition Ceremonies (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Remarks by Brigadier General Richard G. Stilwell 1/12/63
    - Buchanan, NY 5/18/77
    - Montrose, NY 11/24/79
    - Louisville, KY 5/23/86
  - BSA Eagle Scout cards (No.4007) n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Invitation to Join: the National Eagle Scout Association (NESA) (No.30-602) n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Mail-All Alpha List 2/17/78 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Insignias of the NESA (No.30-602) n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Eagletter Vol.2 no.2 4/74 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Letter on NESA guidelines 9/11/87 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - NESA Charter n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Biennial National Conference 1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Special Interest Release: Eagle Scout Bicentennial Celebration 7/75 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Philmont Scout Ranch and Explorer Training Base, New Mexico 1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Dixie Fellowship. Order of the Arrow 75th Anniverary card 1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Scouting for Food Council Information Kit 11/10-17/90 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scout Circus. Red Jacket Coucil, Rochester NY n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Cave Exploring for Scouts. Marengo Cave Park, IN n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Daisy's New Youth Air Pellet and Hunter Education Program n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - The Elements of Scoutmastership: A Training Course for Scout Leaders n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Five Year Progressive Training Program for Local Council Leaders n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Freedom Foundation at Valley Forge n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Keep Him Smiling: Scoutmasters Training Course n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Patrol Leadership Training: A Specialized Course for Scout Leaders n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Purdy Scout Reservation Administration, Conservation, and Training Work Project n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Elements of Scoutmastership and Principles of Scoutmastership First and Second Courses, Cayuga County Council n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Region Ten. Charles L. Sommers Canoe Base n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Reservations for Camp Tom Wooten, Texas n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Scoutleader's Training Course of Newark. Newark, NJ n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Training Before Commissioning n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Troop Camping: A Specialized Course in Troop Camp Leadership n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Wood Badge Men: Wood Badge Training (Reprint from Scouting Magazine, 1948) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - How to Promote Attendance at a District Training Course, Summer Trails Council, Bay City, MI, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Series XII: Calendars
  - LEFAX loose-leaf pocket calendar sheet 1931 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Annual Directory & Calendar. Fenimore Cooper Council, White Plains, NY 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - South Jersery Council pocket calendar 1946 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo Area Council pocket calendars. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Council Calendar 1957-1958
  - Calendar of Events 1962-63
  - Calendar of Events 1964-1965
  - Follow the Rugged Road Fall Roundup Calendar and Goal Chart 1965 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Boy Scouts of America "Come and Get It!" 1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Official Boy Scout Appointment Calendar 1971 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Cub Scout Record 1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "Snoopy's Tribe". Boy Scout Troop 109 Calendar 1980-81 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - A Personal Calendar for the Scoutmaster n.d. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Tomorrow's Leader (Norman Rockwell) personal calendar n.d. (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Series XIII: Maps and Posters
  - The Scout Law poster 1915 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Join Us: Ask A Boy Scout poster 1962 & 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Join Us: Scouting rounds a guy out - Ask a Cub Scout poster 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Scouting's National Advetising Program 1973-74 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Camp Sequoyah Trail Map n.d. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Charles Howell Scout Reservation Map n.d. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Come to Camp Collins poster n.d. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Hang On! Canoe Safety poster n.d. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Outdoor Code poster n.d. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Outdoor Program posters. BSA Camping and Activities Service/BSA Engineering Service n.d. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Presque Isle State Park Map, PA n.d. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Region Two. (2) Map cases n.d (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - San Diego County Riding & Hiking Trails Map n.d. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Swim Fun With Safety poster n.d. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Topographic Map Symbols n.d. (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Series XIV: Miscellania
  - Troop No. 51 Entertainment Program 6/21/17 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Scouter Xmas greeting cards 1934 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - The Ten Mile River Scout Camps brochure (ca. 1942) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - BSA Souvenir Program: Sportsman Show. Burnt Hills-Ballston Lake School, NY 5/3/46 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - The "Step-OM'-eter" 1947 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Region 12 - California mailing envelope (ca. 1953) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - National Council Dedication program. New Brunswick, NJ 6/25/55 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Jubilee Revue Programme. Reading, U.K. 5/16-18/57 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - The Scoutmaster as seen by (cartoon) 8/58 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 50 Years of Dimes to Build Scouting's Commemorative Tribute cardboard dime holder 1959 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Dedication Service for the "Bubba" Carroll Phifer Wagoner Drinking Fountain, Camp Raven Knob 7/15/59 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Dedication Service for the Robert C. Vaughn Chapel 7/4/58 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - BSA and Freedoms Foundation Voting door hanger 11/8/60 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - BSA 50th Anniversary. William D. Boyce cards and envelope, (ca. 1960) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - "Strengthen America" BSA 51st Anniversary Relationships Folder 1961 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - NASA Space Science & Exploration Information Kit. Scoutmaster's Program Aids for BSA (ca. 1961) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Saddlebags Game Specifications 8/21/63 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Magic Learn-To-Trail Cards 1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "Our Troop Plans For 1968-1969" chart (ca. 1968) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "Scout Memorabilia" subscription mailing envelope (ca.1970) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Get into the Spirit of '76/Cub Scouts Quality E cardboard tent (ca. 1976) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "A Promise to Keep" Sustaining Membership Enrollment bumper sticker. Santa Clara County Council, CA (ca. 1976) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Ellsworth H.Augustus International Scout House. North Brunswick, NJ 12/9/75 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "Scouting Together" postcards. Inter-Camp 6/1-4/79 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - The William D. Boyce Trail. Ottawa, IL 6/88 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Art Project Template n.d. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "B. - P's." Last Message n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - BSA folders n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Camping
    - Court of Honor
    - Lectures
    - Organization
    - Training
  - BSA Historical Museum and Nature Trail n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - BSA letterhead n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Central South Carolina Council No. 553 letterhead n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Charter Renewal mailing envelopes n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Compass Game n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Compass signal flag stickers n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cub Scout Bicycle Safety Program stickers n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cub Scouts carboard tent (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Discover Adventure Invitation Cards n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Electros: Excellent Cuts for Use in Promoting Scout Circuses n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - The Flewump Bird n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Games*Tricks*Fires n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Johnston Historical Museum. North Brunswick, NJ n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Lawrence L. Lee Scouting Museum bookmark n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Luminous Pocket Planetarium n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Mafeking Siege Note n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Masonite Plan AE-376 Tote Box and Table n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Morse Code Receiving Card n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - National Council BSA. Supply Service Divsion envelope n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - National Scouting Museum. Murray, KY n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Northeast Georgia Council No. 101 "Scouting rounds a guy out" letterhead n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Nutty-Putt Goofy-Golf n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Pocket Signal Disk envelope n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Round-Up letterhead, Ranch Mortgage and Subpoena n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Salute to the Boy Scouts comic book n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Sea Scouting Folder n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Scout Shop Christmas Card n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Scouter Certificate of Registration Folders n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Scouters Christmas Card n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Scouting/USA stickers n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Scoutmaster, Troop 37, Roanoke, VA identification card n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 75th Diamond Jubilee folders n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Program for the 24th Annual Meeting, Atlanta Area Council 1/16/41 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Six scouting theme bookcovers n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - The Star Spangled Banner n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 33 1/2 R.P.M. records n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Follow the Rugged Road to Adventure
    - Growing Together
  - Timber Is A Crop! Weyerhaeuser Company seed packet n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Washington Irving Council, White Plains, NY Morse Code cards n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Wildlife Identification Quiz - Mammal Tracks and Trails. Ohio Department of Natural Resources n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Series XV: Newsletters, Newspapers, Magazines, Clippings and Photographs
  - "A Bear Fight in the Yellowstone Park". Recreation Vol. XVIII, No. 2, 2/02 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "The Boy Scouts". The Outlook 10/25/13 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "The Boy Scouts of Feudal Japan". The Outlook 9/23/14 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "The Boy Scouts". The Sunday Herald 9/23/17 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "The Boy Scout Movement Investigated By the Religious Education Association". Ninth Annual Report (ca. 1919) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "Boy Scouts, Dined, Give Training Demonstration". Newark Star-Eagle 5/26/20 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - The Scout, Vol. 1, No. 1 2/9/22 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Nature Magazine, Vol. 3, No. 5, May, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Weekly Bulletin of Boy Scout Activities 11/23/25 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Log of the Half Moon. Hendrick Hudson Council, Vol. 1. No. 1 6/26 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "Leading Articles of the Month". The American Review of Reviews (ca. 1926) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Boy Scout Marching Band 1927 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Boy Scouts of the Orange and Maplewood Area, New Jersey 1930-1938 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - The Informant, BSA 1/31 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report. Rockland County Council 1932 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "Lessons fron the Varsity of Life"(by Lord Baden-Powell). Pearson's Magazine 11/32 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - SCOUTING Magazine Bulletins 3/20/33/& 8/9/33 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "Youth Explores Its World". National Geographic Magazine 5/34 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "Hi, Scouts! Love and Geetings from Uncle Dan Beard on his 86th Birthday June 21, 1936". Good Housekeeping 6/36 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Articles mounted on sheet of paper. (ca. 1936-37) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - "Scout Merger In Effect"
    - "Dan Beard, Pioneer In Boy Scout Work, To Speak Here"
    - "Orange Scouters Hear Beard at Camp Dinner"
    - "Dan Beard To Appear At Boy Scout Circus"
  - "National Affairs". Time Magazine, 7/12/37 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - "District Leaders of Scouts to Meet" 11/25/39 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Articles mounted on a sheet of paper (ca.1936-37) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - "Grace Church Memorial Day Sermons Given"
    - "Uncle Dan Beard Finds Boys Today No Worse than Formerly"
    - "Scouts Greet Indian at Mohawk PowWow"
    - "See the Boy Scout Circus"
    - "15th Anniversary of Troop 17"
  - Report of the Scout Committee to the Rector, Wardens, and Vestry of Grace Church 6/28/38 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Articles mounted on a sheet of paper (ca. 1931) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - "Suburban Navy"
    - "Thrilling Rescue of Four in Sound Marks Essex Sea Scouts Cruise"
    - "Sea Scouts of troop Essex with Captain H.E. Powell" (picture)
  - Articles mounted on a sheet of paper (ca.1931, 1937) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - "Four-Year-Old W.O. Boy Drowns on Shore Visit"
    - "Many at Bridge for Camp Fund"
    - "Reports Given on Scout Work"
    - "Radio W.O.R. of Newark, NJ - 'That Boy of Yours'"
    - Letters on W.O.R. rehearsal
  - Council Ring, Vol. XV, No. 23, 6/10/44 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 32nd Annual Report. Fenimore Cooper Council, Inc. 1/26/47 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - "Recovering Drowned Victims". FBI Law Enforcement Bulletin February-March, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Conneticut Circle Magazine 6/51 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - "Toward A Stronger Faith". Scouting 12/51 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - The National Geographic Magazine 9/56 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Sea Scout Ohio River Barge Line Dock Christening 5/57 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - The United States Coast Guard Auxiliary - Certificate of Completion, Basic Small Boat Seamanship (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Explorer scouts and scoutmaster packing car (names identified on back of photograph) 7/21/59 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Reader's Digest Reprints. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - New Horizons in Scouting 3/13/60
    - My Most Unforgettable Character 7/65
    - Exploring - A New Path to a Better America 10/70
  - 1960 Annual Report. Gloucester-Salem Council 12/31/60 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - National Scout Jamboree newspaper clippings 1960-1964 & n.d. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - "Revolution for Youth, Courtesy of the Scouts". American Legion Magazine 1/61 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report. Monmouth Council 6/30/61 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Competitive Rally Bulletin, List of Events, and Newsletter. Rhododendren District, NC 1963 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - "French's 'Remember Maine' Is Sellout In New England". The Independent Press 2/6/64 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - "Boy Scouts Trade - Almost Anything Goes". The Middletown, Ohio, Journal 7/17/64 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - "Wolf Cub Wins All the Badges" Oxford Mail 9/28/66 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Nominating Committee Report. Executive Board of the Naitonal Council 5/22/69 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - "Scout's Labors Are Rewarded" (ca. 1974) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Scouter. Chief Logan Council, Issue 9, November 1977 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - "Putting the outing back into Scouting". Smithsonian, 7/85 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Tarhe Scouting Trails. Shawnee Council, Vol. I, No. 89, January 1989 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "Boys Will Be Scouts". Scouting Equipment Number 16A (Reprint from the American Magazine of June 1927) n.d. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "Building Bamboo Fires - And Brotherhood". Scouting Magazine n.d. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Editorials on BSA. Saturday Evening Post n.d. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Group b.w. photograph on unidentified battleship n.d. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Group b.w. photograph of unidentified Scout Troop Awards ceremony n.d. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "The Guiding Spirit of Olave Baden-Powell". Reader's Digest n.d. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Half- tone photographs. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Troop 17 of Grace Church, Orange, NJ n.d.
    - Unidentified scout in front of Washington Memorial, Washington, D.C. n.d.
    - Unidentified scouts conducting first aid demonstration n.d.
    - Unidentified scouts banking their savings n.d.
  - "Highlights in the Life of Lord Baden-Powell" n.d. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "Ike Stresses Unity in 'Taped' Scout Talks" Los Angeles Examiner n.d. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "Leading Boy Scout Organizations of the U.S.A. Are Located in This Area" Yearbook Oakland Tribune n.d. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - "Morale: The Secret Weapon that Will Win the War" (Boy's Life) n.d. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - " A Nation-Wide Movement For Recreation". The American Review of Reviews n.d. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - News of the Baden-Powell Memorial House n.d. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - North Star News n.d. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - "P.T.A. and the B.S.A.". Scouting Magazine n.d. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - "Patrol Feasts" and "a Look At Spring". Unidentified BSA quarterly n.d. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Region Ten. Charles L. Sommers Wilderness Canoe Base. Crew 723F n.d., b.w. photograph (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Scout House Report (page 2) n.d. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Scout Training for Crippled Boys (Reprint from The Crippled Child of December 1928) n.d. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Troop 17 photographs (2) n.d. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - "Two Happy Scouts". Maxwell House Division n.d. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - "World Scouts". The American Magazine n.d. (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Series XVI: Oversize Miscellania
  - "Quick New Energy Needed" Boy Scout Post Toasties magazine (Ladies Home Journal 7/29) advertisement 1928 (Oversize 9)
  - To the President of the United States of America: Franklin Delano Roosevelt Scout Oath and Law Pledge. Troop 237, Greater New York Council, NY 1/10/41 (Oversize 9)
  - Life Magazine 7/24/50 (Oversize 9)
  - Region 11 Scout Executives Training Conference clipboard 1970 (Oversize 9)
  - "Can't Wait!" (Norman Rockwell) personal calendar 1972 (Oversize 9)
  - Boy Scouts of America calendar 1972 (Oversize 9)
  - 1973 National Scout Jamboree color aerial photo of Moraine State Park, PA 1973 (Oversize 9)
  - BSA American Revolution Bicentennial Declaration table place mat 1976 (Oversize 9)
  - Boy Scouts of America calendar 1976 (Oversize 9)
  - Welcome scouts Jamboree poster. National Scout Jamboree 1977 (Oversize 9)
  - 1989 National Scout Jamboree Public Relations packets 1989 One Hundred Years Ago. "Scouting's Reunion With History" Jamboree poster 7/29/81 (William H. Willcox 1876 painting reproduction) (Oversize 9)
  - "The Strength of Scouting Through Volunteers" Official Boy Scout Calendar 1983 (Oversize 9)
  - Philmont Scout Ranch and Explorer Base topographical map. Cimarron, NM 1986 (Oversize 9)
  - "After Hours" (Csatari) BSA poster n.d. (Oversize 9)
  - Boy Scout Insignia Poster Set n.d. (Oversize 9)
  - Boy Scout 7th National Jamboree color aerial photo of Farragut State Park, Lake Pend Oreille, ID n.d. (Oversize 9)
  - Boy Scout Uniform and Insignia n.d. (Oversize 9)
  - "Can't Wait!" (Norman Rockwell) BSA poster n.d. (Oversize 9)
  - Cub Scout Insignia Poster Set n.d. (Oversize 9)
  - "Eagle Service Project" (Csatari) BSA poster n.d. (Oversize 9)
  - Kandersteg Scout Centre brochures and notecards. Switzerland n.d. (Oversize 9)
  - "To Mom" Cub Scout magazine advertisement for Hallmark Cards n.d. (Oversize 9)
  - "The New Spirit" (Joseph Csatari) BSA poster n.d. (Oversize 9)
  - "Osceola Here We Come!" poster and map n.d. (Oversize 9)
  - Old Colony Council table place mat n.d. (Oversize 9)
  - "Our Aim" poster. Boy Scout Leader Training 8 n.d. (Oversize 9)
  - Region Two. (Oversize 9)
    - Map - New York, New Jersey, Puerto Rico, and the Virgin Islands n.d.
    - Organization & Extension Conference map cases n.d.
  - "The Reunion" (Csatari) BSA poster n.d. (Oversize 9)
  - Scouting/USA table place mat n.d. (Oversize 9)
- Series XVII: Oversize Newspapers
  - The Sunday Herald (Boston, MA) 9/23/17 (Oversize 10)
  - The New York Times (New York, NY) 3/24 &4/7/18 (Oversize 10)
  - Lewiston Journal Magazine Section 5/28/32 (Oversize 10)
  - The Daily Courier (Orange, NJ) 5/18/36 (Oversize 10)
  - The Indianapolis Times (Indianapolis, IN) 9/9/47 (Oversize 10)
  - Linn's Weekly Stamp News 5/28/62 (Oversize 10)
  - Butler Eagle (Butler, PA) Commemorative Issues: 1973 Jamboree East, Morraine State Park, PA 8/3-9/73. (Oversize 10)
    - July 31, 1973
    - August 1-3; 6-9, 1973
  - New Castle News (New Castle, PA) Commenorative Issues: 1973 National Scout Jamboree, Morraine State Park, PA 8/3-9/73. (Oversize 11)
    - July 30-31, 1973
    - August 2-3; 6-9, 1973
  - Pittsburgh Post-Gazette (Pittsburgh, PA). August 3-4, 1973 (Oversize 11)
  - The Pittsburgh Press (Pittsburgh, PA). August 2 & 5, 1973 (Oversize 11)
  - The Washington Times (Washington, D.C.). (Oversize 11)
    - July 23, 1985